msfinancialsavvy.com 2014-02-27

# Privacy statement, Small Business, Learn Investing, mutual funds, personal financial planning, women and money, investment books, loan calculator, retirement.

Disclaimer | Terms of Service | Contact Us | About Us 

### **Privacy Statement**

Because we, at MsFinancialSavvy.com, gather certain types of information about users of our site, we feel you should be aware of the terms surrounding the capture and use of that information. Strong electronic privacy is crucial to the success of the Internet as an online medium. The following discloses what information we gather, how we use or distribute it, and how you can change it.

## **Information We Gather**

We collect statistical information such as page views on an aggregated basis. Such information allows us to find out what areas and content are the most popular on our site. It also allows us to better tailor our content for readers and to help our advertisers understand the demographics of our audience. Aggregated data is essential to keeping MsFinancialSavvy.com free to users. Personal information about you is not obtainable during this process.

**Surveys**

MsFinancialSavvy.com may sometimes conduct surveys to better understand our target audience. We sometimes conduct promotions that are sponsored by advertisers. Aggregated demographic data may be shared during the course of such promotions.

**Newsletters**

MsFinancialSavvy.com offers a free electronic newsletter to our readers. Users voluntarily subscribe to the mailing list by giving their e-mail addresses to us. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by replying to a link provided in the electronic newsletter.

**Message Boards**

Users of MsFinancialSavvy.com message boards must register for these services. During registration, the user is required to supply a username, password, e-mail address, and zip code. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and may be collected and used by others. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**"Email this Article to a Friend" Service**

On some pages at our site, a user may elect to electronically forward an article to a friend by clicking a link on the side navigation bar of the article. The user must provide the email addresses: one for the user and one for the friend. This information is used only to let the recipient know who sent the article.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of data that are written to your hard drive when you visit a web site. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages you've visited or a password so you don't constantly have to re-enter it. A cookie can't read data off of your hard drive or read other cookies created by other web sites. We currently DO NOT use cookies at our site.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We do not control cookies from other outside sites.

**How We Use the Information**

MsFinancialSavvy.com uses your information on an aggregated basis to create traffic reports, deliver marketing messages, and enhance users experience. This also allows us to better anticipate the needs of our users and tailor future content based on users interests. Advertisers will be able to better understand our demographics so they can develop ads that users will find beneficial.

We will not sell your e-mail address or your name and personal demographic information (if requested) to mass marketers or mailing list distributors. We do not share personal information with third parties or affiliates without your explicit consent, period. On particular pages where we have an advertiser-sponsored promotion and request personal information, you will be notified of our intentions.

As stated above, MsFinancialSavvy.com uses e-mail addresses that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters. We may use the mailing list to occasionally send you information or updates from MsFinancialSavvy.com via e-mail. E-mail addresses are also used to log into message board and chat areas. We retain e-mail addresses that were the result of correspondence with users. These include responses to such items as feedback, questions, or subscriptions.

**How You Can Change the Information**

MsFinancialSavvy.com gives its users an option to "Opt Out" of receiving such information as newsletters, tip of the day, etc. Users may remove themselves from the newsletter mailing list by clicking on a "unsubscribe" at the bottom of the email . Users may remove themselves from message board/chat areas by following the specific instructions for that particular area.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We will ensure the proper safeguarding of your personal information.

**Children's Guidelines**

We do not permit minors to answer surveys/polls or log on to message board and chat areas without prior consent of their parents or guardian. We request that minors refrain from using any part of our site that requires the disclosure of personal information unless they have prior permission from parents or guardian. We feel our site is "Safe for Kids", however, it is always a good idea for parents to get involved with their kid's online so they can be aware of what they're doing.

_Note to Kids_ : Make sure you ask your parents or guardian for permission before sending any personal information such as an e-mail address or name to this web site. Make sure your parents read this page as well. 

**Contact Information**

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Any notices that reflect a change will be posted on this page, so check regularly. We hope this privacy policy clarifies our handling of your personal information. If you have any questions about the privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our site, you can contact:

MsFinancialSavvy.com  
PO Box 1385  
Chesapeake, Va.23327-1385  

Also, please read our Disclaimer. Your use of MsFinancialSavvy.com constitutes your acceptance of MsFinancialSavvy.com Terms of Service
